Today is October 7th. It is two years now that Israel has been allowed to enact
its final stage of genocide on the Palestinian people. It is on this day two years ago that
they made a fatal error because it was on this day that Israel thought
that the world would continue to believe their lies as they told them about this day.
And this day two years ago began the downfall of a lunatic society that has plagued the world.
And one day this day will be looked upon as a day of reverence and as a day of celebration
for the beginning of the end. Free Palestine. That said I believe without that said I believe
beyond a shadow of a doubt that Israel knows this and so they are plotting to
expand to the United States. And all this talk about sleeper cells is really them. So I hope that you
all have been paying attention because I feel like a lot of y'all are really caught up in
only one thing that is important. Not realizing that there are multiple things that are important.
support a real one